So a friend of mine,
who's a huge fan of music,
he decided that he was
going to learn the guitar.
And I said to him, well, you know,
if you're going to learn the guitar,
then you should probably take lessons
because you learn a lot quicker,
more quickly. Is it quicker or more
quickly? I'm panicking now about the
grammar.
And he said, oh, no, I don't want to
take lessons. I was like, that's a
bit strange. Why don't you want
to take lessons? And he said, oh,
because I don't want to learn how
to read music. I was like, well,
you know, he's a very educated
guy, like he's not going to have a
problem picking up music notation.
So I said, well, why don't you want
to read music? And he said, oh,
because Paul McCartney doesn't read
music.
I said, well, look,
Paul McCartney is a genius.
You're not a genius.
And so I wouldn't kind of compare
myself to Paul McCartney as I start
playing the guitar.
and this sounds ridiculous but
also kind of this is kind of what
happened to me when I wrote my 20,000
words is that I discovered that I
wasn't a genius I should
have known earlier than that
and then when I discovered
that I wasn't a genius I sulked
and the scene not genius thing comes